(Lee Min Jung)
(Kim Ji Seok)
(OK! Let's Get Divorced)
(All child actor scenes were filmed with a guardian present...)
(with professional staff and in accordance with safety guidelines.)
Won Ho.
Won Ho, can we talk for a minute?
Move.
Wait, hold on.
Right now,
our employees and the production crew...
are all waiting for you. If you say you're not doing it now,
what about all the production costs?
Then what about me? I'm so furious that you tricked me...
that I can't do this show or anything else.
What about me? What am I supposed to do?
Fine, it was all my fault.
I'm so sorry.
I tricked you and made a fool out of you.
That's all my fault. So please, just this once, okay?
No.
Not for me, for our shop.
Stop using the shop as an excuse. This is all about your greed.
This all happened because you were greedy.
So...
you refuse to do it, no matter what?
Yes. Move.
Wait.
I'm not done talking.
What now?
Fine.
I've made my decision.
What was that?
Let's get...
What are you saying? Speak up, I can't hear you.
What did you just do?
Hey, Baek Mi Young.
I mean...
At first, I had no idea what it was.
She suddenly pulled something off her finger and threw it.
I thought, "No way. She has to be joking."
It was a real Cartier.
If it was a real Cartier...
Doesn't that mean she wants a divorce?
Exactly. She's the one who's in the wrong, not me. So why?
What is this? I didn't order it.
It's from the person over there.
She looks pretty young, doesn't she?
No, thank you.
Please tell them we appreciate it, but we have to decline.
We're in the middle of a serious conversation.
Yes, I understand.
Regardless of who's at fault, if she really asks for a divorce...
What are you going to do then?
Well, then I guess we'll have to.
Really?
You'd actually get a divorce?
Goodness.
That Cartier ring... Darn it.
It was a limited edition.
Hey, are you asleep?
If you're awake, we need to talk.
Wait.
I'm not done talking.
What now?
Fine. I've made my decision.
Let's get a divorce.
What was that?
I said, let's get a divorce. Let's do it.
What are you saying? Speak up, I can't hear you.
What did you just do?
Hi, everyone.
Hello.
I know you're all curious about what happened...
after we filmed the show yesterday.
To be honest, my husband and I tried really hard.
But right before the shoot,
I came down with a terrible stomach bug,
so filming has been postponed indefinitely.
It's such a shame, isn't it?
I'm upset, but what can I do?
It's all my fault.
I should have taken better care of myself.
Thank you all so much for your concern.
Tomorrow, I'll be introducing...
this year's new Fall-Winter dress line,
and I'll be back to see you all again.
Yes, I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye.
We need to talk.
About what?
Why did you throw your ring yesterday?
Why? Because I don't need it anymore.
What?
I told you clearly yesterday.
I want a divorce.
Baek Mi Young, get over here right now.
Come here. Let's sit down and talk first. Okay?
Forget it. I don't have time.
But...
Darn it...
I was hoping the show would help the company get back on its feet.
It's a real shame.
It's a shame, but there's nothing we can do.
We just have to keep doing our jobs.
Isn't that right, CEO Ji?
Being on TV wasn't a good fit for us anyway.
But we can barely make payroll next month as it is.
Is that CEO Ji's fault?
It's not like CEO Ji is refusing to pay the employees.
No, what I mean is...
Then what about CEO Baek?
Do you think CEO Baek refused to pay everyone,
and that's why she's trying so hard all by herself?
What do you mean, all by herself?
CEO Ji is doing his best too.
Does someone doing their best...
just blow a huge opportunity and run off?
What do you mean, "run off?"
There will be other opportunities.
Director Song, you're speaking way out of line.
Are you pointing at me?
You're going to hit someone if you keep that up.
Seriously, who do you think you're pointing at?
- Unbelievable. - What are you two doing in here?
- I'm right, aren't I? - Seriously, stop it.
CEO Ji.
Yeong Yu, don't you know how to knock?
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, CEO Ji, but I think you'll want to take this call.
For me?
Yes. When did you have in mind?
Yes, that's possible.
Did you have something in mind?
So the person CEO Ji is on the phone with right now...
is really Cheon Man Ju?
Apparently so.
I'm dying to know why Cheon Man Ju called.
Yes, I understand. Okay.
What did Cheon Man Ju say?
She said she's coming here later for a dress consultation.
- Is it really Cheon Man Ju? - The ultimate icon for Gen Z.
- A celebrity's celebrity. - Is this for real?
Cheon Man Ju is really coming here herself?
- Yes. - Someone famous is coming here?
Did you hear that right?
Was it really Cheon Man Ju?
What, am I deaf? How could I mishear that?
I told you it was Cheon Man Ju.
- Incredible. - This is incredible.
- Cheon Man Ju, for real? - Amazing.
This is huge.
Have you ever seen Cheon Man Ju in person?
So, wait, who is Cheon Man Ju?
- Why? - This is a one-time opportunity.
From now on, just use Cheon Man Ju as an excuse with Mi Young.
- What? - Cheon Man Ju, for a dress fitting,
and what's more important to J&White than her right now?
The divorce?
Is that more important than Cheon Man Ju?
Than the company?
- Of course not. - Exactly.
For the time being, you need to think...
only about Cheon Man Ju.
At least until her wedding is over.
You know who Cheon Man Ju is, right?
Of course you do.
Anyone in this country who doesn't know her must be a spy.
Then you must have been a spy until this morning.
Anyway, for Cheon Man Ju's sake,
let's put this talk about our divorce on hold.
What does Cheon Man Ju have to do with our divorce?
Of course it has something to do with it.
Look, imagine you're Cheon Man Ju.
You come here for the one dress you'll wear in your lifetime,
and what do you find?
The owners are in the middle of a divorce.
They're fighting over whether to get divorced or not.
How about it? Isn't that kind of a turn-off?
Don't you think that's bad luck?
Mi Young, this is a golden opportunity...
to save the company.
We still have to pay our employees next month.
Cheon Man Ju is here.
- I hope you had an easy trip over. - Hello.
Hello. I'm Cheon Man Ju.
A star doesn't drive herself, so that's not an issue.
It's a bit smaller than I expected.
It's my first time.
Did you see Cheon Man Ju?
I did.
What's she like in person?
How should I put it?
Even as a woman, I have to say she has an extraordinary aura.
Gosh, of course.
The man she's marrying...
is one lucky guy.
Goodness.
She had this bag with a jewel on it this big,
- and she was holding it like this. - Really? Incredible.
- And... - Excuse me.
I'm with Cheon Man Ju. Do you happen to know where she is?
Yes, please follow me.
This way.
She looks familiar.
She's my personal photographer.
Hello.
My name is Ahn Hee Ju.
- Yes. - She'll be handling everything...
related to the photography.
I'm a bit particular about my photos,
so I can't just entrust them to anyone.
- These are our sample dresses. - I...
I'm a really big fan of yours, CEO Ji.
I fell completely in love when I saw your dresses.
The dresses are so my style.
Thank you.
This is from the J&White signature line...
You see,
I have this huge fantasy about my wedding dress.
A Dress of a Lifetime that's perfect for me.
That's possible, right?
Of course. It's possible.
A perfectly fitting Dress of a Lifetime.
Look at that confidence.
I definitely came to the right place.
Hee Ju.
I think I'll get my party dress here too.
You're having a party too?
It's before the wedding, so of course.
It's in the suite at the Calvin Hotel.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
(CEO Calvin Kim)
Contract with J&White is finalised.
So now all that's left is to deliver the invitation, right, Calvin?
(Cheon Man Ju)
Okay, this is our fitting room.
Feel free to try anything on, and just let me know.
I'm already so excited.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Have we met somewhere before?
- What? - You just look familiar.
Oh, really?
Right? Where have I seen you?
So you do remember.
By the way, did you turn me down on purpose yesterday?
Yesterday?
You don't remember?
The cocktail.
Cocktail?
What is this? I didn't order it.
It's from the person over there.
Right.
But do you know me?
- What? - Why send me a cocktail...
Think carefully.
The restroom is that way, right?
Man Ju.
You're much slimmer than I expected.
Is that an insult or a compliment?
Don't you think my stomach is sticking out a little?
Your stomach? What are you talking about?
You're so slim.
I'm five months pregnant.
It should look a little different from a regular potbelly.
You've never been pregnant, have you?
So you've never been pregnant.
Congratulations on your pregnancy.
But...
if you're pregnant,
instead of a dress with this silhouette,
how about a bell-line dress that falls from here?
- What did you say? - It'd be a different story...
if you were in the first trimester,
but at this stage,
an A-line dress is too tight and could be dangerous.
And as it happens, this season's trend...
is the bell-line dress as well.
Make it an A-line, no exceptions.
- What? - I'll worry about my own stomach.
Just make the waist tight.
Man Ju, I really can't...
You don't like my belly?
Whatever.
Just do exactly as I say.
You just care about getting paid anyway, right?
I shouldn't have told you I was pregnant.
My pregnancy is a secret.
Yes, of course.
An A-line dress like this is out of the question.
Revise the dress design.
The waist on this is too tight.
Let's go with a bell-line dress with a more comfortable fit.
Why? Didn't you say Cheon Man Ju wanted this one?
And you still think so after seeing her?
This design isn't flattering for her figure at all.
But a bell-line dress has puffs, so it can cover up her flaws.
That's not our call to make.
Our job is to make the dress the client wants...
and make sure they're satisfied.
Then let's just revise the waistline to be a little higher.
Why are you acting like such an amateur?
Be honest with me.
Is it because Cheon Man Ju disrespected you earlier...
that you're pulling a power trip?
Do you really think I'm on a power trip...
with Cheon Man Ju right now?
If this isn't a power trip, what is it?
Didn't you say yourself...
that the client's needs are the top priority?
It's because I made a mistake with Cheon Man Ju.
- A mistake? - Yes, in the fitting room.
I think she chose this dress rashly because of it.
She's going to regret it later.
She won't regret it at all.
Once she sees the dress I made, she'll love it.
Leave the dress to me.
This is a matter of my pride and philosophy.
So,
you refuse to change the design no matter what, is that it?
I'm absolutely not changing it.
Not without a request from Man Ju. Not even if the sky falls.
Then,
do a corset fitting instead of a zipper fitting.
You can do that, can't you?
What's with you?
Since Man Ju will probably gain more weight,
do a corset fitting.
How would you know if Man Ju is going to...
gain weight or not?
I just know.
Man Ju will gain weight even if the sky falls.
So do a corset fitting, understand?
Darn it.
(Punghae Turtle Shrine, Turtle Master)
I pray.
Oh, great spirits, I pray.
Your fate lies across the water.
My gosh.
Yes, that's right.
My son studied abroad.
He went to Milan, Italy, to study fashion.
You're as amazing as they say.
So, what is it you want to ask?
About a baby. My second son's wife.
I want to know when she can have a baby.
All right.
Let's see if a baby is in her future.
It's over.
It has been for a long time.
What?
They were a bad match, blocking each other's fortunes...
and twisting their fates.
They're destined to separate soon.
No, we can't have Won Ho getting a divorce too.
Master, please, take a closer look.
There's no need to look further.
This is all because of your son.
- What about my son? - He committed an unforgivable sin.
That's not true.
My little brother wouldn't hurt a fly.
But his wife isn't exactly blameless either.
Exactly.
Stop beating around the bush...
and tell us straight.
Fine.
Let's see.
Let's take a good, clear look.
Who killed someone?
What did you say?
What? Who killed someone?
Mom, let's go. I think we've seen enough.
- This is ridiculous. - What is this?
Hey. Pay up before you go, you punk.
What? You're calling me a punk?
- Here. Take it, you punk. Let's go. - He's a complete fraud.
"Turtle Master," my foot.
I hope you turn into turtle soup when you die.
- Where did he go? - There.
- Where are you going? Come out. - There.
Come out.
Hey.
- Come out. - Hey, hurry and come out.
- Hey. - I said come out.
- Come out. - Turtle Master, come out.
(To CEO Baek Mi Young)
Oh, right. This is an invitation to my party.
Please make time to come,
even if you have to clear your schedule.
(To CEO Baek Mi Young)
(Cheon Man Ju's Last Solo Party)
(Location: Calvin Hotel, 6:00pm)
Where were you?
I waited for a long time.
I told you not to come back.
Why are you suddenly treating me like this?
Don't do this to me.
I told you, I'm getting married.
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
You know. I...
I'm really all alone now.
What am I supposed to do without you?
She's pregnant.
Three months along.
I don't want to make you feel any more miserable.
(To CEO Baek Mi Young)
(Cheon Man Ju's Last Solo Party)
(Location: Calvin Hotel, 6:00pm)
Are we going to be here all night?
You must have called me here because you have something to say.
Jeez, this guy.
Ji Won Ho.
Answer me, Ji Won Ho.
Yes, I'm listening.
Calvin Kim.
My Mi Young.
Can you make her happy?
"My Mi Young?"
Answer me.
Tell me you'll make her happy!
Gosh, I can't just hit a drunk guy.
I...
My Mi Young.
Of course I'm going to make her happy.
I will never hurt Mi Young the way you did.
I'll make her so happy that she won't even remember...
her time with you. I'll make sure of it.
That promise.
Never forget it.
Because I...
will never forget it either.
(To CEO Baek Mi Young)
You're going to Cheon Man Ju's party?
Yes, I plan on going.
But isn't it at Calvin Hotel?
Are you sure you'll be okay?
What do you mean, am I okay?
Well,
I'm just worried you might run into Calvin there.
- I'm just worried. - It'd be a little awkward, I guess.
But what can I do? It's all in the past.
I guess so.
Hey.
Calvin got a divorce.
A divorce?
Yes.
There was an article about it a while ago.
Mi Young?
Oh, here are some beads...
What's wrong with that?
You postponed your divorce because of Cheon Man Ju.
So for her to go to a party Man Ju is throwing...
is only natural, don't you think?
Well, that's true. That's true, but...
Of all places, the party is at...
The party being at the Calvin Hotel is what's bothering you?
Because it's obvious she'll run into Calvin there.
It's been a while since she broke up with Calvin.
And that was before she met you.
They only dated for a short while, right?
What?
Was it more serious?
No, it's nothing like that.
If not, what are you worried about?
Besides, even if Calvin is divorced now,
do you really think he'd hit on her?
Not when you're by her side.
He's divorced?
You didn't know?
When did he get divorced?
Do you even live in this country?
But then,
you didn't even know who Cheon Man Ju was.
Of course you wouldn't know.
So that jerk Calvin got a divorce?
Unbelievable.
Are you happy with the bust length?
Yes. If we add a tulle overlay here,
it'll look more natural, elegant, and beautiful.
Something with floral details like this would suit you too.
This one, or if we put this on the front...
Because it will draw the eyes away from the face.
Will this line work? Now, as for the off-the-shoulder...
Hi, everyone. Yes, hello.
I have some really big news for you all today.
Do you know who visited our shop?
I should wait until we have over 300 viewers to tell you.
We passed it.
The person who visited our shop was...
Drumroll, please. Cheon Man Ju.
For her wedding dress,
Cheon Man Ju chose our very own J&White.
(J&White and Cheon Man Ju are a killer combination.)
I'm so excited to see the dress Cheon Man Ju will be wearing.
We're going to present a truly legendary dress,
so please look forward to it.
(Are you going to Cheon Man Ju's party today?)
(CEO, are you going to the party?)
Cheon Man Ju's party?
(You have to tell us all about it. Can't wait for the pictures.)
Of course. I have to go.
Where do you think you're going?
What kind of married woman just goes to a hotel?
Are you out of your mind?
My husband is so old-fashioned.
Well then, I'll tell you all about it...
when I'm back. He's not angry.
What do you think you're doing?
And you? Are you crazy?
Thinking of going to the Calvin Hotel?
What about the Calvin Hotel?
What's wrong with going to the Calvin Hotel?
Have you already forgotten what kind of person Calvin is?
He cheated on you with another woman,
got that other woman pregnant,
and then married her.
And Calvin recently got divorced.
When I heard that jerk got divorced,
why did I get such a bad feeling?
- I just got a chill down my spine. - So what's your point?
I said I'm going to the Calvin Hotel.
Did I say I was going to a hotel with Calvin?
Who knows? That jerk might approach you again.
What if he tries to harm you?
- What if? - Geez.
What? Harm me?
Isn't this a complete double standard?
- Double standards? - Yes, double standards.
Whatever harm Calvin could possibly do to me now,
compared to how you've torn my heart out all this time,
it would be a drop in the bucket.
- Baek Mi Young. - Stop meddling in my business.
Mind your own business.
Darn it.
Hello.
- Little Dumplings. Hi. - Hi.
You all know today's my party, right?
(Today's dress is going to be legendary.)
Stop telling me how pretty I am.
In a few hours,
this place is going to be completely packed.
I'm just so excited.
Oh, my. Ms. Lin Zhao Ming.
Gosh, being invited to a party like this,
I'm so happy I could die, don't you think?
(Are you okay? This is insane.)
Surprise. Were you surprised?
I wanted to express with my whole body...
that I'm so happy I could just fall over.
Okay, my Little Dumplings. I'll see you all later.
- Bye. - Bye.
- Bye. - See you again.
I'm so dumbfounded.
I was in the middle of a live stream,
and he just burst out of the room...
and started yelling, "Are you crazy? Going to the Calvin Hotel?"
He was just going completely ballistic.
Seriously. I couldn't believe it.
Is CEO Ji jealous or something?
Jealous? Don't be ridiculous.
It's like no matter what I do,
he's just dying to sabotage it.
He's the absolute worst.
Oh, yes.
By the way,
- what are you going to wear later? - What?
I mean, Calvin...
No. You're going to Cheon Man Ju's party.
You can't just wear anything.
Well, I have an outfit in mind.
What? What are you going to wear?
- Have you seen me in this before? - Let me see.
No.
- This is too plain. - You think so?
Let's not do that.
Since you're going, you should get all dressed up.
You might run into Calvin.
Just a minute ago, you were worried about me seeing Calvin.
No, what I mean is,
if you're going to run into him anyway,
you should show up looking drop-dead gorgeous.
That's what I'm saying.
Make Calvin sick with regret for letting you go.
What?
Oh, give me a break.
Is she the star of the party or something?
Cheon Man Ju is the one getting married, not her.
What's wrong, man?
What, is she supposed to wear sweats to a party?
What's wrong with sweats?
She was invited because of work.
She should just throw something on and go.
Oh, come on.
That's ridiculous.
The more I think about it, the more pissed I get.
Some of us are covered in thread,
working ourselves to the bone, while others get all dolled up...
and just think about going to a party.
This isn't right.
This really isn't right.
Hey.
Hey, where are you going?
Oh, seriously.
Oh my gosh.
Oh my...
You brought all the fabric from the shop.
So,
you're telling me...
- to organise all of this today? - Yes. By colour and design,
please organise and sort all of it.
If you focus, it won't even take 3 or 4 hours.
What? Three or four hours?
I told you.
I have plans tonight.
Work comes before your evening plans.
That's why I don't make plans,
- so I can work. - Are you kidding me right now?
So you're not going to work?
Ji Won Ho, what is wrong with you?
You just keep getting more and more petty.
Petty? Are you done talking?
No, I'm not done. What are you going to do about it?
Go on. Say it.
Hey, you're being petty and pathetic.
I'm pathetic? Work first...
- Is working hard pathetic? - You're disgusting.
This is negligence of duty.
Going to that party is work for me.
You don't have time. Get to it.
Hey, you...
I guess you'd better work hard.
Vice President Kang.
Seriously, what's wrong with CEO Ji?
What about CEO Ji?
He just dropped a bombshell on Mi Young.
A work bombshell.
I mean, she's going to Cheon Man Ju's party today.
And he knows that perfectly well.
I mean, he's treating her like Cinderella or something.
Don't you think CEO Ji is being way too spiteful?
I completely understand where CEO Ji is coming from.
- What? - If it were me,
putting everything else aside,
the name of the party venue alone would upset me.
For example, Director Song,
if your ex-husband's name was plastered all over a hotel...
What does my ex-husband have to do with this?
Pardon?
There's zero chance of that happening.
Who would name a hotel the Bong Gu Hotel?
Her ex-husband's name is Bong Gu?
I'm sorry, Director Song.
What are you doing, you jerk?
That scared me.
What a messed-up dream that was.
I need to get it together.
Glad you could make it.
Is everything delicious?
It's a pleasure.
Hello.
Oh my, you're here.
This is my fiancé.
Hello. It's a pleasure to meet you.
Yes, my sincerest congratulations on your marriage.
I hope I didn't put you in an awkward position...
by asking you to come.
Not at all. Of course I had to come.
Are you...
looking for someone?
Not at all. No.
Well, then, please enjoy yourself.
- Okay. - Shall we go upstairs?
Hi there, my Little Dumplings.
Okay, this is where I'm having my pre-wedding party.
What do you think of the party decorations?
Isn't it so pretty?
What? You think I'm prettier?
(Cheon Man Ju has the best taste.)
Ta-da.
What do you think of my dress? It's so pretty, right?
But you know what?
The dress I'll be wearing on my wedding day...
is even prettier than this one.
(We want to see the dress.)
(Show us the dress.)
You want to see it now?
Hold on.
Darn it. This is so distracting, I can't work.
CEO Ji.
This is Man Ju.
Yes, Ms. Man Ju.
Is Man Ju's dress finished?
The dress?
Yes, the dress is finished. Why?
Well, I want to try it on soon today.
Quickly.
You want to try on the dress today?
Yes, right now.
Right now?
Yes.
(Cheon Man Ju's Last Solo Party, Location: Calvin Hotel, 6:00pm)
Please just go.
I don't want to make you feel any more miserable.
Mi Young.
Yes. It's been a while.
It really has been a long time.
Delivery for someone here?
Oh, there you are.
Well, long time no see, Mr. Calvin.
He looks scared.
Nothing happened, right?
What do you mean?
Never mind.
Not that it could've happened. Not with so many people watching.
What are you doing here all of a sudden?
- Well... - I ordered it.
Hello.
I had to try on my dress today,
so I pestered CEO Ji about it.
Right now?
That was some fast delivery.
I guess you ride a motorcycle.
Yes. Speed and accuracy are the lifeblood of delivery.
Here you are. Perfectly prepared, just as you ordered.
The special finishing touch is a gift from me.
Oh, I'm so excited.
- Let's go. - What?
Let's go quickly.
Wait...
Can we talk for a minute?
Man Ju, are you almost ready?
I'm ready.
Ta-da.
- What do you think? - It looks amazing on you.
I like it.
But I think the waistline could be more defined.
Something's just not quite right.
But did you not see it?
The special finishing touch I prepared?
Wait a minute.
A finishing touch? There's a finishing touch?
Sure.
- I found it. - That, yes, that's it.
Oh, so this is it. Quick, put it on me.
Okay, I got it.
Hold on, I will do it.
As tight as possible.
There we go.
It's so beautiful.
I'm going to go show this off.
What did you want to say?
The invitation you got from Man Ju.
I was the one who sent it.
You did?
Why?
Because I missed you.
I have really missed you.
You missed me.
So what?
What's going to change just by us looking at each other?
Look,
from now on, just pretend you don't know me.
To me,
you are like someone who doesn't exist.
I'm going to go now.
Are you happy?
Are you?
Of course.
You saw my husband, didn't you?
I'm...
doing very well.
I'm incredibly happy.
CEO Ji.
You don't recognise me?
What?
Take a closer look.
Don't you remember me?
Are you hitting on me?
What?
That's strange.
You look so young. Why are you using such an old-fashioned pickup line?
Look, I'm sorry, but you're not my type at all.
- What? - Stop playing games.
And I'm only saying this because you remind me of my little sister,
but you shouldn't mess with a married man.
You could get into real trouble.
Milan.
- What? - Don't you remember?
Eight years ago, in Milan.
Milan?
If we look at these models,
accessories from the new collection would really make them stand out.
Yes, I agree. The material and the design...
are both important. What do you think?
- I completely agree. - Thank you.
Excuse me, I'm just going to use the restroom.
Of course, go ahead.
Where do you think you're going?
Excuse me, you're Korean, right?
I remember now.
That kid from Milan. No, the pickpocket.
You make it sound like I'm a pickpocket.
I can't believe we're meeting here like this.
You've really changed a lot.
So much that I almost didn't recognise you.
Have I changed that much?
Anyway, it's good to see you.
So, that's why you sent me that cocktail?
What the heck? I almost got the wrong idea.
Maybe it wasn't a misunderstanding.
What?
Everyone, isn't my dress gorgeous?
Especially this belt.
It's so pretty, right?
Ta-da.
I'm so excited.
I want to dance.
Her acting is amazing.
You totally had me fooled.
- She's a really good actress. - She's incredible.
She's really good.
She's incredible.
Man Ju.
Man Ju, stay with me.
Hey, someone call 911, quickly.
I think it's real.
Man Ju, stay with me.
I like you.
- What? - I'm interested in you.
Didn't I just tell you I'm a married man?
So what? I just said that I like you.
(Paramedics)
Man Ju, what's wrong?
What happened?
Just a moment.
I have to go. We'll talk later.
Make way. Everyone, please clear the area.
They said Man Ju was pregnant. And that she was full-term.
Then let's just revise the waistline to be a little higher.
Why are you acting like such an amateur?
Since Man Ju will probably gain more weight,
do a corset fitting.
How would you know if Man Ju is going to gain weight or not?
I just know.
Man Ju will gain weight even if the sky falls.
So do a corset fitting, understand?
(Restricted Area: Operating Room)
The surgery was a success.
Both the mother and baby are healthy.
Thank goodness.
That is such a relief.
Yes.
(VIP Two Patient Name: Cheon Man Ju)
Man Ju, you did great.
Have you seen my daughter?
Yes.
What is she like?
She's beautiful.
She looks just like you.
But I'm just hopeless, aren't I?
What do you mean?
All for a slim waist.
My poor baby...
How trapped must she have felt in there?
She must have barely been able to breathe.
(OB-GYN)
Yes, Mom? I'm busy, so just tell me.
You brat.
So you're really going through with the divorce?
What are you talking about? Divorce?
That vixen Mi Young says she's going to divorce you.
The divorce papers were just served at the motel.
What? Divorce papers?
Why was I so worried about what others would think?
Because I was focused on such pointless things,
I almost never got to see my own baby.
I really don't deserve to be a mother.
That's not true.
Man Ju.
You saved your baby.
You saved her.
That's all that matters.
No.
I'm not the one who saved my baby.
It was you, CEO Baek.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I almost never got to see my own baby.
I really don't deserve to be a mother.
Can't you please not go today?
I'm sorry. Today's the last day. It will all be over today.
I'll be back soon.
- Please save my baby. - Ma'am, please calm down.
Please calm down.
Please save her.
When we lost Dallae,
you weren't there for us.
I still...
I still feel like Dallae is right here.
I'm not the one who saved my baby.
It was you, CEO Baek.
Mommy is so sorry. I'm so sorry I couldn't protect you.
Look,
I really don't want to say this at a time like this,
but how could you serve me with divorce papers...
Are you satisfied now?
What?
Does seeing Cheon Man Ju like that make you feel better?
Hey, that's not a fair thing to say.
Are you saying that what happened to Cheon Man Ju...
is because of my dress?
Well, wasn't it?
I told you so many times that we needed to change that dress.
Well, you should have just told me you were pregnant.
You're the one who said...
you would never back down, not even if the sky fell.
You never listen to a word I say. I can tell you again and again,
hundreds or even thousands of times,
- but you do whatever you want. - Is that why...
you filed for divorce?
And you sent them to my mother's house?
Hey, let's just be completely honest here.
What did I do to you that was so wrong?
Go read them.
I listed out everything you did wrong.
What do you mean, go read them? Just tell me right here.
You're a murderer.
What?
Hey, Baek Mi Young, get back here.
No.
You're worse than a murderer.
(Epilogue)
Please, just help me this one time.
I really don't care if it's a son or a daughter.
So if you could please just help me this one time,
I'll live an honest and good life, all right?
I'll work hard and be diligent. So please, just this once...
Come here, Mi Young.
Come here.
Oh, my.
It's okay.
- It's okay. Don't cry. - Honey.
I know. It's okay.
I...
I'm pregnant.
I know.
What?
Wait, this... If it has two lines...
That means you're pregnant, right? You're pregnant...
Are you pregnant? You're pregnant?
Wait, so does this mean we're finally going to be parents?
You and I are going to be a mom and dad?
I'm going to be a dad.
Mi Young, you've been through so much.
(Special Thanks to Lee Su Ji for Her Guest Appearance)
(OK! Let's Get Divorced)
So then, CEO Ji,
you have no objections to my decision?
This is a bomb just waiting to go off.
I have no idea when, where, or how it'll explode.
Are you having fun?
Aren't you?
I want this trunk show to be a success to prove a point.
Forget it. The finale model has to be Hee Ju.
If you really hate that idea,
then withdraw the divorce papers.
Separate from our relationship,
I want to prove myself properly.